hello my name is joe brewer and i'm the
director of cognitive policy works if
you're watching this it probably means
you're worried about the future of our
country I know I am this year's election
demonstrated just how precarious things
have become for the United States in the
midst of the worst recession in a
century with global warming beating down
our door and millions out of work we saw
that our political process is utterly
failing the American people now more
than ever we need to mobilize everyone
who believes in the high ideals that
once made this country great civil
liberties democracy the sacredness of
our natural bounty and the inherent
goodness of our people I would like to
invite you to participate in an
experiment in democracy this project is
about setting America on solid ground
during turbulent times I'm a
professional strategy consultant who has
advised Attorney General's labor unions
environmental NGOs and a host of other
progressive organizations I'd like to
offer my services along with my
colleagues sir Robinson and Eric Haas
and draft a guidebook to help
progressives everywhere to understand
the fundamental threats that we're up
against and reveal a path forward that
can finally unite us during our time of
need will you put a few dollars into the
creation of the progressive agenda isn't
it finally time we took matters into our
own hands and started the difficult work
of repairing or below broken political
system I'd like to see hope restore the
real change is not only possible but
inevitable that's why we all need to
rise up as leaders and take back our
country now is the time for action and
I'd like to help pave the way and I
can't do it without you thank you